export default data = [
  {
      question: "When dining at a restaurant, we need to be ______ of other customers and keep our conversations at an appropriate noise level. ",
      options: ["peculiar","defensive","noticeable","considerate"],
      correct_option: "considerate"
  },
  {
      question: "John shows ______ towards his classmates. He doesn’t take part in any of the class activities and doesn’t even bother talking to other students in his class. ",
      options: ["indifference","sympathy","ambiguity","desperation"],
      correct_option: "indifference"
  },
  {
      question: "To meet the unique needs of the elderly, the company designed a cell phone ______ for seniors, which has big buttons and large color displays. ",
      options: ["necessarily","relatively","specifically","voluntarily"],
      correct_option: "specifically"
  },
  {
      question: "A well-constructed building has a better chance of ______ natural disasters such as typhoons, tornadoes, and earthquakes. ",
      options: ["undertaking","conceiving","executing","withstanding"],
      correct_option: "withstanding"
  },
  {
      question: "Our family doctor has repeatedly warned me that spicy food may ______ my stomach, so I’d better stay away from it.",
      options: ["irritate","liberate","kidnap","override"],
      correct_option: "irritate"
  },
  {
      question: "Because the new principal is young and inexperienced, the teachers are ______ about whether he can run the school well. ",
      options: ["passionate","impressive","arrogant","skeptical"],
      correct_option: "skeptical"
  },
  {
      question: "Many universities offer a large number of scholarships as an ______ to attract outstanding students to enroll in their schools.",
      options: ["ornament","incentive","emphasis","application"],
      correct_option: "incentive"
  },
  {
      question: "Since Diana is such an ______ speaker, she has won several medals for her school in national speech contests.",
      options: ["authentic","imperative","eloquent","optional"],
      correct_option: "eloquent"
  },
  {
      question: "The candidate made energy ______ the central theme of his campaign, calling for a greater reduction in oil consumption. ",
      options: ["evolution","conservation","donation","opposition"],
      correct_option: "conservation"
  },
  {
      question: "Concerned about mudslides, the local government quickly ______ the villagers from their homes before the typhoon hit the mountain area.",
      options: ["evacuated","suffocated","humiliated","accommodated"],
      correct_option: "evacuated"
  },
]